Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
If
لو
Tang Yuyan finds out
تانغ يويان يكتشف
not only are you not her real mother,
ليس فقط أنك لست والدتها الحقيقية،
but also the one who killed her father,
ولكن أيضا من قتل والدها،
how would she feel?
كيف ستشعر؟
What exactly do you want?
ماذا تريد بالضبط؟
To become the head of the Tang Family,
ليصبح رئيسًا لعائلة تانغ،
you must be clever.
يجب أن تكون ذكيا.
What I want—
ما أريده—
you surely know it.
أنت تعرف ذلك بالتأكيد.
How is it?
كيف هذا؟
Let's talk outside.
دعونا نتحدث في الخارج.
Her pulse is weak,
نبضها ضعيف
but still fairly steady.
ولكن لا تزال ثابتة إلى حد ما.
It's less a coma,
إنها أقل من غيبوبة،
more like she's just asleep.
أشبه بأنها نائمة فقط.
That's good.
هذا جيد.
I didn't expect
لم اتوقع
you could read pulses.
يمكنك قراءة النبضات.
My mom is amazing.
أمي مذهلة.
Doctors often came to ask her advice.
وكان الأطباء يأتون إليها في كثير من الأحيان لطلب النصيحة.
I picked up a little bit over time.
لقد التقطت القليل مع مرور الوقت.
This is all my fault.
كل هذا خطئي.
If I hadn't tossed the address away,
لو لم أرمي العنوان بعيدًا،
Xiao Duo wouldn't have found it.
شياو دوو لن يجده.
It's not your fault.
إنه ليس خطؤك.
That's just how Xiao Duo is.
هكذا هو شياو دوو.
Even if she couldn't find the address,
حتى لو لم تتمكن من العثور على العنوان،
she'd find another way.
ستجد طريقة أخرى.
Besides,
بجانب،
if not for Xiao Duo,
إن لم يكن لشياو دو،
we wouldn't have survived.
لم نكن لننجو.
Xiao Duo called out "Brother" before fainting.
نادى شياو دو "أخي" قبل أن يغمى عليه.
Tell me,
أخبرني،
why was she silent before?
لماذا كانت صامتة من قبل؟
Could it be related to her power?
هل يمكن أن يكون ذلك مرتبطًا بقوتها؟
Brother
أخ
Xiao Duo
شياو ديو
When will Xiao Duo wake up?
متى سوف يستيقظ شياو دو؟
She might need a full checkup at the hospital.
قد تحتاج إلى فحص كامل في المستشفى.
But I guess
ولكنني أعتقد
they won't have a clear answer.
لن يكون لديهم إجابة واضحة.
I'll take her to get checked now.
سوف آخذها للفحص الآن.
Xiao Duo
شياو ديو
The door is locked.
الباب مغلق.
No, something's wrong.
لا، هناك شيء خاطئ.
Something must've happened.
لابد أن شيئاً قد حدث.
Move aside.
تنحى جانبا.
Let me kick the door open.
دعني أركل الباب مفتوحا.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
Brother
أخ
Xiao Duo
شياو ديو
Open the door!
افتح الباب!
Xiao Duo, open up!
شياو دوو، افتح!
You must've seen how I looked.
يجب أن تكون قد رأيت كيف بدا لي.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'll leave on my own.
سأغادر بمفردي.
Xiao Duo
شياو ديو
What are you saying?
ماذا تقول؟
I know I looked scary.
أعلم أنني كنت أبدو مخيفًا.
I don't know
لا أعرف
why I turned out this way.
لماذا أصبحت بهذه الطريقة.
My aunt said
قالت عمتي
I caused my parents' deaths.
لقد تسببت في وفاة والدي.
Brother Meng
الأخ منغ
Sister Yuyan
الأخت يويان
Sister Yuer
الأخت يوير
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I never meant to hurt you.
لم أقصد أن أؤذيك أبدًا.
Xiao Duo, don't say such nonsense.
شياو دوو، لا تقل مثل هذا الهراء.
Me and Brother Meng,
أنا والأخ منغ،
and Sister Yuer, would never blame you.
والأخت يوير، لن تلومك أبدًا.
You protected us.
لقد حميتنا.
Xiao Duo
شياو ديو
Please open the door.
من فضلك افتح الباب.
Open the door.
افتح الباب.
Brother
أخ
Are you afraid of Xiao Duo?
هل أنت خائف من شياو دوو؟
Xiao Duo
شياو ديو
I'm the real bad guy.
أنا الرجل السيئ الحقيقي.
When we first met,
عندما التقينا لأول مرة،
you gave me your only food.
لقد أعطيتني طعامك الوحيد.
But I stayed with you
ولكنني بقيت معك
because being near you boosted my power.
لأن وجودي بالقرب منك عزز قوتي.
That's why I followed you.
لهذا السبب اتبعتك.
I wanted to use you at first.
لقد أردت استخدامك في البداية.
Xiao Duo
شياو ديو
Will you be my little sister?
هل ستكونين أختي الصغيرة؟
Back then,
في ذلك الوقت،
I didn't lead you on the right path,
لم أرشدك إلى الطريق الصحيح،
I used you to hide my identity.
لقد استخدمتك لإخفاء هويتي.
I dragged you into petty theft.
لقد جررتك إلى السرقة البسيطة.
I'm the one who did wrong.
أنا من أخطأ.
All these years,
كل هذه السنوات،
we've relied on each other.
لقد اعتمدنا على بعضنا البعض.
I've always seen you as my real sister.
لقد رأيتك دائمًا كأختي الحقيقية.
Xiao Duo
شياو ديو
You can scold me,
يمكنك توبيخني
or hit me,
أو اضربني
but
لكن
please don't leave me.
من فضلك لا تتركني.
Xiao Duo
شياو ديو
We have no home now.
ليس لدينا منزل الآن.
You're all I have left.
أنت كل ما تبقى لي.
I won't cry.
لن أبكي.
Young Master Shen
السيد الشاب شين
Why
لماذا
did they all say
هل قالوا جميعا
the Shen Family could cure this child?
هل يمكن لعائلة شين علاج هذا الطفل؟
We couldn't help her,
لم نستطع مساعدتها
so we sent her to your family.
فأرسلناها إلى عائلتك.
Didn't the Shen Family promise us
ألم تعدنا عائلة شين؟
to treat her kindly?
لمعاملتها بلطف؟
Young Master Shen, please!
السيد الشاب شين، من فضلك!
The Master's will is like the dawn;
إن إرادة السيد مثل الفجر؛
it cannot be obscured.
لا يمكن إخفاؤه.
This is
هذا هو
Xiao Duo's sealed memory.
ذاكرة شياو دو المختومة.
Those who stand in the way—
أولئك الذين يقفون في الطريق-
like moths eating clothes,
مثل العث يأكل الملابس،
or fire burning fields—
أو حقول مشتعلة بالنار—
will be reduced to nothing.
سوف يتم تقليصها إلى لا شيء.
You brought me
لقد احضرتني
a brat meant to target me,
طفل مدلل كان من المفترض أن يستهدفني،
and expect me to keep her?
وتتوقع مني أن أحتفظ بها؟
You're asking for death.
أنت تطلب الموت.
Ah!
اه!
Child, run!
يا طفل، أركض!
Run!
يجري!
Run, child!
أركض يا طفلي!
Don't look back!
لا تنظر للخلف!
Kill her!
اقتلوها!
Run!
يجري!
So this is the secret Xiao Duo hid.
إذن هذا هو السر الذي أخفاه شياو دو.
Her power
قوتها
can even nullify Shen Jingshi's power.
يمكن أن تلغي حتى قوة شين جينغشي.
I always said you were a monster.
لقد قلت دائمًا أنك وحش.
Had your parents send you away.
لقد أرسلك والديك بعيدًا.
Go on, leave.
إذهب، إذهب.
We can't handle you.
نحن لا نستطيع التعامل معك.
Okay.
تمام.
I won't cry.
لن أبكي.
Xiao Duo, you can't leave now.
شياو دوو، لا يمكنك المغادرة الآن.
Come on, Xiao Duo.
هيا، شياو دو.
I'll take you to eat something tasty.
سأأخذك لتناول شيء لذيذ.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Xiao Duo
شياو ديو
Go inside first, okay?
اذهب إلى الداخل أولاً، حسنًا؟
Go lie down and rest a bit.
اذهب واستلقي واستريح قليلاً.
I'll come find you soon.
سأأتي إليك قريبا.